
const quizData = 
[
    {
      id: '001',
      question: 'In the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God',
      options: ['John 3:16', 'John 1:1', 'John: 5:7'],
      answer: 'John 1:1'
    },
    {
      id: '002',
      question: 'For the word of God is quick and powerful, and sharper than any two-edged sword, piercing even to the division of soul and spirit, and of joints and marrow, and is a discerner of the thoughts and intents of the heart',
      options: ['Hebrews 12:4', 'Hebrews 4:12', 'Hebrews: 4:4'],
      answer: 'Hebrews 4:12'
    },
    {
      id: '003',
      question: 'Ye are the light if the World, a city set on a hill cannot hid',
      options: ['Matthew 5:5', 'Matthew 14:5', 'Matthew 5:14'],
      answer: 'Matthew 5:14'
    },
    {
      id: '004',
        question: 'The Lord is my Shepherd, I shall not want',
        options: ['Psalm 23:1', 'Psalm 1:2', 'Psalm 1:1'],
        answer: 'Psalm 23:1'
      },
      { 
        id: '005',
        question: 'For God so loved the world that He gave His only begotten Son, that whoever believes in Him should not perish but have everlasting life',
        options: ['John 3:6', 'John 3:16', 'John 16:3'],
        answer: 'John 3:16'
      },
      {
        id: '006',
        question: 'Therefore take up the whole armor of God, that you may be able to withstand in the evil day, and having done all, to stand',
        options: ['Ephesians 6:12', 'Ephesians 6:13', 'Ephesians 6:18'],
        answer: 'Ephesians 6:13'
      },
      { 
        id: '007',
        question: 'And do not be drunk with wine, in which is excess; but be filled with the Spirit',
        options: ['Ephesians 5:18', 'Ephesians 4:18', 'Ephesians 6:18'],
        answer: 'Ephesians 5:18'
      },
      { 
        id: '008',
        question: 'Finally, brethren, whatever things are true, whatever things are noble, whatever things are just, whatever things are pure, whatever things are lovely, whatever things are of good report, if there is any virtue and if there is anything praiseworthy think on these things',
        options: ['Ephesians 2:18', 'Philippians 4:8', 'Philippians 4:6'],
        answer: 'Philippians 4:8'
      },
      { 
        id: '009',
        question: 'Do not touch My anointed ones, and do My prophets no harm',
        options: ['Psalms 105:15', 'Psalms 105:5', 'Psalms 115:5'],
        answer: 'Psalms 105:15'
      },
      { 
        id: '010',
        question: 'Nay in all these things we are more than conquerors through Him who loved us',
        options: ['Romans 8:30', 'Romans 8:37', 'Acts 8:37'],
        answer: 'Romans 8:37'
      },
      { 
        id: '011',
        question: 'There is therefore now no condemnation to those who are in Christ Jesus, who do not walk according to the flesh, but according to the Spirit',
        options: ['Romans 8:6', 'Romans 8:8', 'Romans 8:1'],
        answer: 'Romans 8:1'
      },
      { 
        id: '012',
        question: 'Come to Me, all you who labor and are heavy laden, and I will give you rest',
        options: ['Matthew 11:28', 'Matthew 28:11', 'Matthew 11:11'],
        answer: 'Matthew 11:28'
      },
      { 
        id: '013',
        question: 'I can do all things through Christ who strengthens me',
        options: ['Phillipians 4:13', 'Phillipians 4:19', 'Isaiah 60:1'],
        answer: 'Phillipians 4:13'
      },
      { 
        id: '014',
        question: 'And my God shall supply all your need according to His riches in glory by Christ Jesus',
        options: ['Phillipians 1:1', 'Phillipians 4:6', 'Phillipians 4:19'],
        answer: 'Phillipians 4:19'
      },
      { 
        id: '015',
        question: 'Blessed are the poor in spirit, for theirs is the kingdom of heaven',
        options: ['Matthew 5:3', 'Matthew 7:7', 'Mark 5:3'],
        answer: 'Matthew 5:3'
      },
      { 
        id: '016',
        question: 'He who believes in Me, as the Scripture has said, out of his heart will flow rivers of living water',
        options: ['John 7:38', '1 John 7:38', 'John 1:1'],
        answer: 'John 7:38'
      },
      { 
        id: '017',
        question: 'Behold, the hand of the Lord is not short, that it cannot save; nor His ear heavy, that it cannot hear',
        options: ['Isaiah 60:22', 'Isaiah 60:1', 'Isaiah 59:1'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 59:1'
      },
      { 
        id: '018',
        question: 'A little one shall become a thousand, and a small one a strong nation. I, the Lord, will hasten it in its time',
        options: ['Isaiah 60:1', 'Isaiah 60:22', 'Isaiah 60:2'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 60:22'
      },{ 
        id: '019',
        question: '....they that who know their God shall be strong, and do great exploits.',
        options: ['Daniel 11:11', 'Daniel 11:32', 'Daniel 11:35'],
        answer: 'Daniel 11:32'
      },
      { 
        id: '020',
        question: 'They that observe lying vanities shall forsake their own mercy',
        options: ['Genesis 2:8', 'Jonah 2:8', 'Jonah 2:1'],
        answer: 'Jonah 2:8'
      },{ 
        id: '021',
        question: 'But they that wait on the Lord Shall renew their strength; they shall mount up with wings like eagles, they shall run and not be weary, they shall walk and not faint',
        options: ['Isaiah 40:31', 'Isaiah 40:29', 'Isaiah 60:1'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 40:31'
      },
      { 
        id: '022',
        question: 'For unto us a Child is born, unto us a Son is given; and the government will be upon His shoulder. And His name will be called Wonderful, Counselor, Mighty God Everlasting Father, Prince of Peace',
        options: ['Isaiah 9:6', 'Isaiah 6:9', 'Isaiah 9:9'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 9:6'
      },{ 
        id: '023',
        question: 'He was wounded for our transgressions, He was bruised for our iniquities; the chastisement for our peace was upon Him, and by His stripes we are healed',
        options: ['Isaiah 40:29', 'Isaiah 53:7', 'Isaiah 53:5'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 53:5'
      },
      { 
        id: '024',
        question: 'So shall My word be that goes forth from My mouth; It shall not return to Me void, but it shall accomplish what I please, and it shall prosper in the thing for which I sent it',
        options: ['Isaiah 55:10', 'Isaiah 55:11', 'Psalm 91:7'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 55:11'
      },
      { 
        id: '025',
        question: 'A thousand may fall at your side, and ten thousand at your right hand; but it shall not come near you',
        options: ['Psalm 91:1', 'Psalm 91:7', 'Psalm 91:9'],
        answer: 'Psalm 91:7'
      },{ 
        id: '026',
        question: 'Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil; for You are with me; Your rod and Your staff, they comfort me',
        options: ['Psalm 23:4', 'Psalm 23:1', 'Psalm 23:6'],
        answer: 'Psalm 23:4'
      },
      { 
        id: '027',
        question: 'He shall be like a tree planted by the rivers of water, that brings forth its fruit in its season, whose leaf also shall not wither; and whatever he does shall prosper',
        options: ['Psalm 1:1', 'Psalm 1:3', 'Psalm 3:1'],
        answer: 'Psalm 1:3'
      },
      { 
        id: '028',
        question: 'You shall tread upon the lion and the cobra, the young lion and the serpent you shall trample underfoot',
        options: ['Romans 8:1', 'Psalm 91:13', 'Psalm 91:16'],
        answer: 'Psalm 91:13'
      },{ 
        id: '029',
        question: 'Ye are a chosen generation, a royal priesthood, an holy nation, a peculiar people; that ye should shew forth the praises of him who hath called you out of darkness into his marvellous light',
        options: ['1 Peter 2:9', '2 Peter 2:9', '1 Peter 1:1'],
        answer: '1 Peter 2:9'
      },
      { 
        id: '030',
        question: 'Therefore take up the whole armor of God, that you may be able to withstand in the evil day, and having done all, to stand',
        options: ['Ephesians 6:13', 'Ephesians 6:10', 'Ephesians 6:18'],
        answer: 'Ephesians 6:13'
      },
      { 
        id: '031',
        question: 'For we do not wrestle against flesh and blood, but against principalities, against powers, against the rulers of the darkness of this world, against spiritual hosts of wickedness in the heavenly places',
        options: ['Revelation 7:12', 'Ephesians 6:12', 'Ephesians 6:1'],
        answer: 'Ephesians 6:12'
      },{ 
        id: '032',
        question: 'Grow in the grace and knowledge of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ. To Him be the glory both now and forever. Amen',
        options: ['2 Peter 1:1', '1 Peter 3:18', '2 Peter 3:18'],
        answer: '2 Peter 3:18'
      },
      { 
        id: '033',
        question: 'Amen! Blessing and glory and wisdom, thanksgiving and honor and power and might, be to our God forever and ever. Amen',
        options: ['Genesis 7:12', 'Revelation 7:12', 'Acts 7:12'],
        answer: 'Revelation 7:12'
      },
      { 
        id: '034',
        question: 'This Book of the Law shall not depart from your mouth, but you shall meditate in it day and night, that you may observe to do according to all that is written in it. For then you will make your way prosperous, and then you will have good success',
        options: ['Jonah 1:8', 'Joshua 1:1', 'Joshua 1:8'],
        answer: 'Joshua 1:8'
      },
      { 
        id: '035',
        question: 'In the beginning God created the heavens and the earth',
        options: ['Genesis 1:1', 'John 1:1', 'Revelation 22:21 '],
        answer: 'Genesis 1:1'
      },
      { 
        id: '036',
        question: 'He took the damsel by the hand, and said unto her, Talitha cumi; which is, being interpreted, Damsel, I say unto thee, arise',
        options: ['John 3:16', 'Mark 5:41', 'Matthew 3:3'],
        answer: 'Mark 5:41'
      },
      { 
        id: '037',
        question: 'looking unto Jesus, the author and finisher of our faith, who for the joy that was set before Him endured the cross, despising the shame, and has sat down at the right hand of the throne of God',
        options: ['Hebrews 4:12', 'Hebrews 12:2', 'Hebrews 1:1 '],
        answer: 'Hebrews 12:2'
      },
      { 
        id: '038',
        question: 'Having been perfected, He became the author of eternal salvation to all who obey Him',
        options: ['Hebrews 5:9', 'John 1:1', 'Hebrews 1:1'],
        answer: 'Hebrews 5:9'
      },
      { 
        id: '039',
        question: 'Let us therefore come boldly to the throne of grace, that we may obtain mercy and find grace to help in time of need',
        options: ['Genesis 1:1', 'Romans 1:1', 'Hebrews 4:16'],
        answer: 'Hebrews 4:16'
      },
      { 
        id: '040',
        question: 'Therefore, if anyone is in Christ, he is a new creation; old things have passed away; behold, all things have become new',
        options: ['2 Corinthians 5:17', '1 Corinthians 5:17', 'John 10:10'],
        answer: '2 Corinthians 5:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '041',
        question: 'The thief does not come except to steal, and to kill, and to destroy. I have come that they may have life, and that they may have it more abundantly',
        options: ['John 10:10', 'Matthew 10:10', 'Mark 7:7'],
        answer: 'John 10:10'
      },
      { 
        id: '042',
        question: 'That if thou shalt confess with thy mouth the Lord Jesus, and shalt believe in thine heart that God hath raised him from the dead, thou shalt be saved',
        options: ['John 3:16', 'Romans 10:9', '1 Peter 2:9'],
        answer: 'Romans 10:9'
      },
      { 
        id: '043',
        question: 'and if children, then heirs; heirs of God and joint heirs with Christ, if indeed we suffer with Him, that we may also be glorified together',
        options: ['Romans 8:17', 'Romans 8:8', 'James 1:1'],
        answer: 'Romans 8:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '044',
        question: 'He shall cover you with His feathers, and under His wings you shall take refuge; His truth shall be your shield and buckler',
        options: ['Psalm 91:15', 'Psalm 91:4', 'Psalm 91:1'],
        answer: 'Psalm 91:4'
      },
      { 
        id: '045',
        question: 'Ye are of God, little children, and have overcome them: because greater is he that is in you, than he that is in the world',
        options: ['2 John 4:4', '1 John 4:4', 'John 4:4'],
        answer: '1 John 4:4'
      },
      { 
        id: '046',
        question: 'For My thoughts are not your thoughts, nor are your ways My ways,” says the Lord',
        options: ['Isaiah 55:8', 'Isaiah 9:6', 'Joshua 1:8'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 55:8'
      },
      { 
        id: '047',
        question: 'Herein is our love made perfect, that we may have boldness in the day of judgment: because as he is, so are we in this world',
        options: ['2 John 4:17', 'John 4:17', '1 John 4:17'],
        answer: '1 John 4:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '048',
        question: 'Peace, be still!” And the wind ceased and there was a great calm.',
        options: ['Mark 4:39', 'Mark 4:4', 'Matthew 4:39'],
        answer: 'Mark 4:39'
      },
      { 
        id: '049',
        question: 'Believe in the Lord your God, and you shall be established; believe His prophets, and you shall prosper',
        options: ['2 Chronicles 20:20', 'Matthew 11:28', 'Exodus 1:1'],
        answer: '2 Chronicles 20:20'
      },
      { 
        id: '050',
        question: 'Arise, shine; for your light has come! and the glory of the Lord is risen upon you',
        options: ['Isaiah 60:2', 'Isaiah 60:1', 'Isaiah 40:29'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 60:1'
      },
      { 
        id: '051',
        question: 'being confident of this very thing, that He who has begun a good work in you will complete it until the day of Jesus Christ;',
        options: ['Philippians 1:6', 'Philippians 6:1', 'Philippians 1:2'],
        answer: 'Philippians 1:6'
      },
      { 
        id: '052',
        question: 'No weapon that is formed against thee shall prosper; and every tongue that shall rise against thee in judgment thou shalt condemn. This is the heritage of the servants of the Lord, and their righteousness is of me, saith the Lord',
        options: ['Isaiah 60:2', 'Isaiah 54:17', 'Isaiah 17:54'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 54:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '053',
        question: 'Behold, I will do a new thing; now it shall spring forth; shall ye not know it? I will even make a way in the wilderness, and rivers in the desert',
        options: ['Isaiah 43:19', 'Matthew 5:8', 'Isaiah 7:4'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 43:19'
      },
      { 
        id: '054',
        question: 'Thou shalt not be afraid for the terror by night; nor for the arrow that flieth by day;',
        options: ['Psalm 91:15', 'Psalm 91:5', 'John 10:10'],
        answer: 'Psalm 91:5'
      },
      { 
        id: '055',
        question: 'Be ye therefore perfect, even as your Father which is in heaven is perfect',
        options: ['1 Peter 2:9', 'Matthew 48:5', 'Matthew 5:48'],
        answer: 'Matthew 5:48'
      },
      { 
        id: '056',
        question: 'Be ye therefore merciful, as your Father also is merciful',
        options: ['Luke 6:36', 'Luke 6:38', 'Exodus 1:3'],
        answer: 'Luke 6:36'
      },
      { 
        id: '057',
        question: 'Ye shall receive power, after that the Holy Ghost is come upon you: and ye shall be witnesses unto me both in Jerusalem, and in all Judaea, and in Samaria, and unto the uttermost part of the earth',
        options: ['Acts 8:1', 'Acts 1:8', 'Acts 8:3'],
        answer: 'Acts 1:8'
      },
      { 
        id: '058',
        question: 'And these signs shall follow them that believe; In my name shall they cast out devils; they shall speak with new tongues',
        options: ['Mark 16:7', 'Mark 15:5', 'Mark 16:17'],
        answer: 'Mark 16:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '059',
        question: 'Give, and it shall be given unto you; good measure, pressed down, and shaken together, and running over, shall men give into your bosom. For with the same measure that ye mete withal it shall be measured to you again',
        options: ['Luke 6:38', 'Luke 38:6', 'Luke 6:3'],
        answer: 'Luke 6:38'
      },
      { 
        id: '060',
        question: 'For with the heart man believeth unto righteousness; and with the mouth confession is made unto salvation',
        options: ['Romans 10:37', 'Romans 10:9', 'Romans 10:10'],
        answer: 'Romans 10:10'
      },
      { 
        id: '061',
        question: 'A wise son maketh a glad father: but a foolish son is the heaviness of his mother',
        options: ['Proverbs 10:2', 'Proverbs 10:1', 'Philippians 6:2'],
        answer: 'Proverbs 10:1'
      },
      { 
        id: '062',
        question: 'So then faith cometh by hearing, and hearing by the word of God',
        options: ['Romans 10:17', 'Romans 8:1', 'Romans 8:6'],
        answer: 'Romans 10:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '063',
        question: 'For to be carnally minded is death; but to be spiritually minded is life and peace',
        options: ['Psalm 1:1', 'Romans 8:8', 'Romans 8:6'],
        answer: 'Romans 8:6'
      },
      { 
        id: '064',
        question: 'Ask, and it shall be given you; seek, and ye shall find; knock, and it shall be opened unto you',
        options: ['Mark 7:7', 'Matthew 7:7', 'Matthew 8:8'],
        answer: 'Matthew 7:7'
      },
      { 
        id: '065',
        question: "For if by one man's offence death reigned by one; much more they which receive abundance of grace and of the gift of righteousness shall reign in life by one, Jesus Christ",
        options: ['Romans 1:1', 'Romans 5:17', 'Romans 5:7'],
        answer: 'Romans 5:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '066',
        question: 'I am the vine, ye are the branches: He that abideth in me, and I in him, the same bringeth forth much fruit: for without me ye can do nothing',
        options: ['John 5:5', 'John 15:5', 'John 15:7'],
        answer: 'John 15:5'
      },
      { 
        id: '067',
        question: 'Honour thy father and mother; which is the first commandment with promise',
        options: ['Ephesians 6:2', 'Ephesians 6:1', 'Ephesians 6:3'],
        answer: 'Ephesians 6:2'
      },
      { 
        id: '068',
        question: 'Unto thee, O Lord, do I lift up my soul',
        options: ['Psalm 25:1', 'Psalm 23:1', 'Psalm 105:1'],
        answer: 'Psalm 25:1'
      },
      { 
        id: '069',
        question: 'He giveth power to the faint; and to them that have no might he increaseth strength',
        options: ['Isaiah 40:31', 'Isaiah 40:29', 'Isaiah 40:30'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 40:29'
      },
      { 
        id: '070',
        question: 'For if I pray in an unknown tongue, my spirit prayeth, but my understanding is unfruitful',
        options: ['1 Corinthians 5:17', '1 Corinthians 4:4', '1 Corinthians 14:14'],
        answer: '1 Corinthians 14:14'
      },
      { 
        id: '071',
        question: 'I am the good shepherd: the good shepherd giveth his life for the sheep',
        options: ['John 10:11', '1 John 2:11', 'John 3:1'],
        answer: 'John 10:11'
      },
      { 
        id: '072',
        question: 'Rejoice in the Lord always: and again I say, Rejoice',
        options: ['Philippians 4:4', 'Philippians 4:5', 'Ephesians 4:4'],
        answer: 'Philippians 4:4'
      },
      { 
        id: '073',
        question: 'If ye abide in me, and my words abide in you, ye shall ask what ye will, and it shall be done unto you',
        options: ['John 5:7', 'John 15:6', 'John 15:7'],
        answer: 'John 15:7'
      },
      { 
        id: '074',
        question: 'Ye are the salt of the earth: but if the salt have lost his savour, wherewith shall it be salted? it is thenceforth good for nothing, but to be cast out, and to be trodden under foot of men',
        options: ['Matthew 5:13', 'Matthew 5:7', 'Matthew 5:15'],
        answer: 'Matthew 5:13'
      },
      { 
        id: '075',
        question: 'the fruit of the Spirit is love, joy, peace, longsuffering, gentleness, goodness, faith',
        options: ['Galatians 5:2', 'Galatians 5:22', '2 Corinthians 5:17'],
        answer: 'Galatians 5:22'
      },
      { 
        id: '076',
        question: 'I am crucified with Christ: nevertheless I live; yet not I, but Christ liveth in me: and the life which I now live in the flesh I live by the faith of the Son of God, who loved me, and gave himself for me',
        options: ['Galatians 2:22', 'Galatians 2:20', 'Romans 1:8'],
        answer: 'Galatians 2:20'
      },
      { 
        id: '077',
        question: 'For whatsoever is born of God overcometh the world: and this is the victory that overcometh the world, even our faith',
        options: ['John 5:4', '1 John 5:4', '2 John 5:4'],
        answer: '1 John 5:4'
      },
      { 
        id: '078',
        question: 'Now faith is the substance of things hoped for, the evidence of things not seen',
        options: ['Hebrews 11:1', 'Hebrews 1:1', 'Hebrews 4:12'],
        answer: 'Hebrews'
      },
      { 
        id: '079',
        question: 'Jesus saith unto him, I am the way, the truth, and the life: no man cometh unto the Father, but by me',
        options: ['John 14:6', 'John 7:7', 'John 14:4'],
        answer: 'John 14:6'
      },
      { 
        id: '080',
        question: 'He that cometh from above is above all: he that is of the earth is earthly, and speaketh of the earth: he that cometh from heaven is above all',
        options: ['1 John 3:31', 'John 3:31', 'Mark 3:31'],
        answer: 'John 3:31'
      },
      { 
        id: '081',
        question: 'For I am not ashamed of the gospel of Christ: for it is the power of God unto salvation to every one that believeth; to the Jew first, and also to the Greek',
        options: ['Romans 1:16', 'Acts 1:8', 'Romans 1:8'],
        answer: 'Romans 1:16'
      },
      { 
        id: '082',
        question: 'What manner of man is this, that even the wind and the sea obey him?',
        options: ['Revelations 20:20', 'Mark 4:41', 'Mark 4:38'],
        answer: 'Mark 4:41'
      },
      { 
        id: '083',
        question: 'For the earnest expectation of the creature waiteth for the manifestation of the sons of God',
        options: ['Romans 8:6', 'Matthew 7:8', 'Romans 8:19'],
        answer: 'Romans 8:19'
      },
      { 
        id: '084',
        question: 'Giving thanks unto the Father, which hath made us meet to be partakers of the inheritance of the saints in light: Who hath delivered us from the power of darkness, and hath translated us into the kingdom of his dear Son:',
        options: ['Colossians 1:12-13', 'Colossians 1:12', 'Colossians 1:13'],
        answer: 'Colossians 1:12-13'
      },
      { 
        id: '085',
        question: 'Seest thou a man diligent in his business? he shall stand before kings; he shall not stand before mean men',
        options: ['Proverbs 10:1', 'Proverbs 22:29', 'Proverbs 22:1'],
        answer: 'Proverbs 22:29'
      },
      { 
        id: '086',
        question: 'For unto you is born this day in the city of David a Saviour, which is Christ the Lord',
        options: ['Luke 2:10', 'Luke 2:11', 'Mark 2:11'],
        answer: 'Mark 4:41'
      },
      { 
        id: '087',
        question: 'Thou comest to me with a sword, and with a spear, and with a shield: but I come to thee in the name of the Lord of hosts, the God of the armies of Israel, whom thou hast defied',
        options: ['1 Samuel 17:45', 'Proverbs 17:45', '1 Kings 4:38'],
        answer: '1 Samuel 17:45'
      },
      { 
        id: '088',
        question: 'I am the bread of life: he that cometh to me shall never hunger; and he that believeth on me shall never thirst',
        options: ['John 16:17', 'John 6:3', 'John 6:35'],
        answer: 'John 6:35'
      },
      { 
        id: '089',
        question: 'Jesus answered and said unto him, Verily, verily, I say unto thee, Except a man be born again, he cannot see the kingdom of God',
        options: ['Psalm 20:20', 'John 3:3', 'Acts 1:1'],
        answer: 'John 3:3'
      },
      { 
        id: '090',
        question: 'This is my beloved Son, in whom I am well pleased',
        options: ['Matthew 3:17', 'Matthew 3:7', 'John 3:17'],
        answer: 'Mark 4:41'
      },
      { 
        id: '091',
        question: ' While the earth remaineth, seedtime and harvest, and cold and heat, and summer and winter, and day and night shall not cease',
        options: ['Genesis 20:20', 'Genesis 22:8', 'Genesis 8:22'],
        answer: 'Genesis 8:22'
      },
      { 
        id: '092',
        question: 'Giving thanks unto the Father, which hath made us meet to be partakers of the inheritance of the saints in light',
        options: ['Corinthians 1:12', 'Colossians 1:12', 'Matthew 11:28'],
        answer: 'Colossians 1:12'
      },
      { 
        id: '093',
        question: 'For the weapons of our warfare are not carnal, but mighty through God to the pulling down of strong holds',
        options: ['Genesis 1:2', '2 Corinthians 10:10', '2 Corinthians 10:4'],
        answer: '2 Corinthians 10:4'
      },
      { 
        id: '094',
        question: 'What shall we then say to these things? If God be for us, who can be against us?',
        options: ['Romans 8:31', 'Acts 6:3', 'Matthew 5:48'],
        answer: 'Romans 8:31'
      },
      { 
        id: '095',
        question: 'This I say then, Walk in the Spirit, and ye shall not fulfil the lust of the flesh',
        options: ['Galatians 5:16', 'Matthew 1:1', 'John 3:16'],
        answer: 'Galatians 5:16'
      },
      { 
        id: '096',
        question: 'The first man is of the earth, earthy; the second man is the Lord from heaven',
        options: ['Isaiah 40:31', '1 Corinthians 15:47', 'Daniel 11:32'],
        answer: '1 Corinthians 15:47'
      },
      { 
        id: '097',
        question: 'Casting down imaginations, and every high thing that exalteth itself against the knowledge of God, and bringing into captivity every thought to the obedience of Christ',
        options: ['2 Corinthians 10:5', 'Mark 115:5', 'Psalm 91:15'],
        answer: '2 Corinthians 10:5'
      },
      { 
        id: '098',
        question: 'For, behold, the darkness shall cover the earth, and gross darkness the people: but the Lord shall arise upon thee, and his glory shall be seen upon thee',
        options: ['Isaiah 60:3', 'Isaiah 60:2', 'Isaiah 60:1'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 60:2'
      },
      { 
        id: '099',
        question: 'Fear thou not; for I am with thee: be not dismayed; for I am thy God: I will strengthen thee; yea, I will help thee; yea, I will uphold thee with the right hand of my righteousness',
        options: ['Isaiah 41:10', 'Matthew 5:7', '1 Peter 2:9'],
        answer: 'Isaiah 41:10'
      },
      { 
        id: '100',
        question: 'Thy word is a lamp unto my feet, and a light unto my path',
        options: ['Psalm 119:100', 'Psalm 119:105', 'John 11:35'],
        answer: 'Psalm 119:105'
      },
      { 
        id: '101',
        question: 'Casting all your care upon him; for he careth for you',
        options: ['James 2:20', '1 Peter 5:7', 'Matthew 4:4'],
        answer: '1 Peter 5:7'
      },
      { 
        id: '102',
        question: 'Now the just shall live by faith: but if any man draw back, my soul shall have no pleasure in him',
        options: ['Hebrews 10:38', 'Proverbs 10:1', '1 John 4:4'],
        answer: 'Hebrews 10:38'
      },
      { 
        id: '103',
        question: 'My brethren, count it all joy when ye fall into divers temptations',
        options: ['Genesis 1:2', 'Ephesians 6:10', 'James 1:2'],
        answer: 'James 1:2'
      },
      { 
        id: '104',
        question: 'But ye are come unto mount Sion, and unto the city of the living God, the heavenly Jerusalem, and to an innumerable company of angels',
        options: ['Hebrews 12:22', 'Joshua 1:8', 'Hebrews 11:1'],
        answer: 'Hebrews 12:22'
      },
      { 
        id: '105',
        question: 'He that loveth pleasure shall be a poor man: he that loveth wine and oil shall not be rich',
        options: ['Acts 1:8', 'John 3:16', 'Proverbs 21:17'],
        answer: 'Proverbs 21:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '106',
        question: 'Beloved, now are we the sons of God, and it doth not yet appear what we shall be: but we know that, when he shall appear, we shall be like him; for we shall see him as he is',
        options: ['Philippians 2:9', '1 John 3:2', 'Psalm 102:13'],
        answer: '1 John 3:2'
      },
      { 
        id: '107',
        question: 'For his anger endureth but a moment; in his favour is life: weeping may endure for a night, but joy cometh in the morning',
        options: ['Psalm 30:5', 'Psalm 105:5', 'Romans 10:10'],
        answer: 'Psalm 30:5'
      },
      { 
        id: '108',
        question: 'But without faith it is impossible to please him: for he that cometh to God must believe that he is, and that he is a rewarder of them that diligently seek him',
        options: ['Hebrews 11:1', 'Hebrews 11:6', 'Hebrews 4:12'],
        answer: 'Hebrews 11:6'
      },
      { 
        id: '109',
        question: 'According as his divine power hath given unto us all things that pertain unto life and godliness, through the knowledge of him that hath called us to glory and virtue',
        options: ['2 Peter 1:3', 'Mark 4:4', '2 Corinthians 7:4'],
        answer: '2 Peter 1:3'
      },
      { 
        id: '110',
        question: 'Before I formed thee in the belly I knew thee; and before thou camest forth out of the womb I sanctified thee, and I ordained thee a prophet unto the nations',
        options: ['Jeremiah 1:5', 'Philippians 2:14', 'James 1:2'],
        answer: 'Jeremiah 1:5'
      },
      { 
        id: '110',
        question: 'For the kingdom of God is not meat and drink; but righteousness, and peace, and joy in the Holy Ghost',
        options: ['Mark 11:22', 'Romans 14:17', 'Psalm 1:3'],
        answer: 'Romans 14:17'
      },
      { 
        id: '111',
        question: 'Train up a child in the way he should go: and when he is old, he will not depart from it',
        options: ['Proverbs 22:6', 'Proverbs 22:17', 'Matthew 11:28'],
        answer: 'Proverbs 22:6'
      },
      { 
        id: '112',
        question: 'The Lord is not slack concerning his promise, as some men count slackness; but is longsuffering to us-ward, not willing that any should perish, but that all should come to repentance',
        options: ['2 Peter 3:9', '2 Corinthians 3:9', 'John 10:10'],
        answer: '2 Peter 3:9'
      },
      { 
        id: '113',
        question: 'To every thing there is a season, and a time to every purpose under the heaven:',
        options: ['Revelations 1:1', 'Ecclesiastes 3:1', 'Proverbs 22:6'],
        answer: 'Ecclesiastes 3:1'
      },
      { 
        id: '114',
        question: 'But we all, with open face beholding as in a glass the glory of the Lord, are changed into the same image from glory to glory, even as by the Spirit of the Lord',
        options: ['2 Corinthians 3:18', 'Luke 1:26', 'Matthew 4:4'],
        answer: '2 Corinthians 3:18'
      },
      { 
        id: '115',
        question: 'The lines are fallen unto me in pleasant places; yea, I have a goodly heritage',
        options: ['Romans 5:8', 'Psalm 16:16', 'Psalm 16:6'],
        answer: 'Psalm 16:6'
      },
      { 
        id: '116',
        question: 'And that he died for all, that they which live should not henceforth live unto themselves, but unto him which died for them, and rose again',
        options: ['2 Corinthians 5:15', 'Proverbs 22:6', 'John 3:17'],
        answer: '2 Corinthians 5:15'
      },
      { 
        id: '117',
        question: 'Wherefore God also hath highly exalted him, and given him a name which is above every name',
        options: ['Acts 19:20', 'Philippians 2:9', 'Psalm 1:1'],
        answer: 'Philippians 2:9'
      },
      { 
        id: '118',
        question: 'Finally, my brethren, be strong in the Lord, and in the power of his might',
        options: ['Galatians 2:20', 'Ephesians 6:10', 'Hebrews 11:1'],
        answer: 'Ephesians 6:10'
      },
      { 
        id: '119',
        question: 'There is none holy as the Lord: for there is none beside thee: neither is there any rock like our God',
        options: ['1 Samuel 2:2', '2 Samuel 2:2', 'Acts 9:38'],
        answer: '1 Samuel 2:2'
      },
      { 
        id: '120',
        question: 'Bless the Lord, O my soul: and all that is within me, bless his holy name',
        options: ['Psalm 105:15', 'Psalm 103:1', 'Psalm 103:5'],
        answer: 'Psalm 103:1'
      },
    
  ]

  export default quizData;
